cash Prosperity campaign by Prudential
Assurance Malaysia barad campaign period
1st January 2025 till 28th February 2025
featured product Pro with you
eligibility requirements one the policy
holder life assured of an eligible
policy must be a new customer from the
Prudential agency channel two meet the
minimum annual premium of 2,400 ring
three opt in for recurring payments via
credit or debit card by 17th of March
2025 cash rewards 88 ring
additional rewards earn more rewards
when you enhance your protection with
the following one attach a medical Rider
100 ring extra cash reward two attach a
medical booster 100 ring extra cash
reward three attach a critical illness
Rider with a sum assured of at least
$100,000 100 ring extra cash reward four
select a policy term with coverage until
at least age next birthday 80 by 17
March 2025 100 ring extra cash reward
total cash rewards up to 488 ring it
boost your protection celebrate the new
year and enjoy a prosperous 2025 with
Prudential for more details contact hre
today